<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.ietr.preesm.feature"
      label="Preesm Feature"
      version="0.6.0"
      provider-name="IETR/INSA">

   <description url="http://preesm.sf.net">
      PREESM provides a complete framework for fast prototyping. PREESM
stands for Parallel &amp; Real-time Embedded Executives Scheduling
Method. It generates a simulation and an optimized multiprocessor
code from graph descriptions of algorithm and architecture.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright or © or Copr. 
IETR/INSA: Matthieu Wipliez, Jonathan Piat, Maxime Pelcat,
Jean-François Nezan, Mickaël Raulet
[mwipliez,jpiat,mpelcat,jnezan,mraulet]@insa-rennes.fr
   </copyright>

   <license>
      This software is a computer program whose purpose is to prototype
parallel applications.
This software is governed by the CeCILL-C license under French
law and abiding by the rules of distribution of free software.
You can use, modify and/or redistribute the software under the
terms of the CeCILL-C license as circulated by CEA, CNRS and
INRIA at the following URL &quot;http://www.cecill.info&quot;.
As a counterpart to the access to the source code and rights
to copy, modify and redistribute granted by the license, users
are provided only with a limited warranty and the software&amp;apos;s
author, the holder of the economic rights, and the successive
licensors have only  limited liability.
In this respect, the user&apos;s attention is drawn to the risks associated
with loading, using, modifying and/or developing or reproducing
the software by the user in light of its specific status of free
software, that may mean that it is complicated to manipulate,
and that also therefore means that it is reserved for developers
and experienced professionals having in-depth computer knowledge.
Users are therefore encouraged to load and test the software&apos;s
suitability as regards their requirements in conditions enabling
the security of their systems and/or data to be ensured and,
more generally, to use and operate it in the  same conditions
as regards security. 
The fact that you are presently reading this means that you have
had knowledge of the CeCILL-C license and that you accept its
terms.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="PREESM" url="http://preesm.sourceforge.net/eclipse/"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="org.ietr.preesm.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.ietr.preesm.plugin.codegen"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.ietr.preesm.plugin.mapper"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.ietr.preesm.plugin.transforms"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.ietr.preesm.plugin.architransform"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.sf.dftools.workflow"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
